Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
That shit!
- Hello!
- So. did you ask 'em?
- Yep. They said fine.
Oh. good!
Sure it's okay with your mom.
though. right?
Yeah. she doesn't care.
She's working.
Isn't she coming up this weekend?
I don't know.
So come on. how cute is he?
Spit it out.
- Oh. he's kind of gorgeous.
- Yeah?
He's sort of like a cousin. but not
really. He wants to be a forest ranger.
Oh. good! Well. then after dinner we could set a
fire in your room. and he can come and rescue us.
You should've seen the look
on her face.
I never laughed so hard. I swear to God.
I just can't believe you might miss it.
Hi. Gulliver.
How you doin'. boy?
Hey. Pilgrim.
Come here.
Hey. babe.
You're such a beautiful boy.
What are you thinkin'?
What are you thinkin'. boy?
You wanna go for a ride?
Let's go for a ride.
Come on. Come on. boy. Come on.
- Hello?
- It's me.
- Hi.
- So what train are you taking?
- I should be in by 2:00.
Okay.
You want me to pick you up?
No. I can take a cab.
Grace go riding?
What do you want to do
about dinner?
- I hadn't thought.
- I can ask to try that place Emily says...
- Oh. hang on.
- They're here. so...
I'll let you go. We'll figure it out
when you get here. okay?
Yeah. okay. Okay. Bye. Hello?
Please! Oh. God. please!
Oh. wait. Have you seen that
stupid cereal commercial? It's like...
- And where are the paintings? It's about her work. and we can't even see it.
- But we're trying to...
We can change the colour of the deck. and we can
move it up so then you can see the paintings...
We need to see the paintings.
She's an artist.
- Have you checked on her going rate?
- Gottschalk.
Yes. The legal department's
on that right now.
- David!
- Did you speak to Felton?
Yes. we're suing.
Well. is that absolutely necessary?
It'll just make it a bigger story.
- Am I on the speaker?
- David. he signed an agreement that he wouldn't talk to the press...
and now he's libelled me
by saying I faked the figures.
- You're not going soft on me. are you?
- Well. nothing like a good public feud.
Exactly!
- You know that kid Adam?
- Yeah.
- He's very cute!
- I think you'd make a good couple. Grace.
- I don't think so.
- Oh. I do!
- You think he's cute?
- Are you serious?
- I think he's cute.
- Oh. I think he's lucky that he lives next door to you.
- I think. I think I...
- What do you think?
I think you have a crush on him.
All right. let's take a shortcut.
Let's take a shortcut.
- You know. we can't even read it.
- Friday is confirmed.
- Right. okay.
No. no. no. no. no. no.
We have to reshoot this.
- I said it. I said it.
- I said that.
- It's "that." It's "that."
- I said it
- I swear to God. it's "that." It's "that."
- It. it. it. it!
- All right. fine. Let's start again. Ready?
- All right. fine. fine. fine.
All right. I met him at a party
And he told me how to drive
He said he'd like to do it backwards
I said it... It...
- Come on.
- Judith.
I said it... It!
Come on!
Gulliver. Gulliver. up!
Up. Gulliver!
- Judith!
- Hey! No! No. no. no!
Grace. look out!
- Pilgrim! Judith. Judith!
- Grace!
Hello!
No!
Gulliver!
Gulliver. stop!
Hold it. Gulliver!
Gulliver! Come on!
Robert.
Judith's dead.
And what about Grace?
- She's in pretty bad shape.
- It's a multiple trauma.
- Where is she?
- She's still in the O.R.
- O.R.? What for?
- It's just... It's...
It's a mid-shaft. tib-fib fracture with a vascular
compromise. meaning the blood supply to the lower leg...
They think they have to take part
of the leg off.
Which leg?
The right leg.
Oh. Jesus.
Okay.
Just take it easy.
This is gonna be tough on both of us.
So let's not make it any harder
than it has to be.
Judith.
- That bag's almost empty.
- Oh. they'll be in to change it.
If you leave it up to these people...
Excuse me.
- My daughter needs a new I.V.
- Yes. I know. We have her down.
Well. I'd like it
taken care of now. please.
You have to stay on top
of these people constantly.
I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
We really should let her get some rest.
and I do have to change the bandage.
You can come back in a couple of hours
and see how she's doing.
Mrs MacLean? Mrs MacLean. you have a call
on line two. You can take it right there.
- Hello?
- Annie. it's Liz. How's Grace?
Her leg was very damaged.
and they had to remove it.
Oh. God. Annie. I'm so sorry.
Listen. I. I know
that you're being hit with a lot now...
and it's hard to think about anything else.
but I have to talk to you about Pilgrim.
Hello?
Yeah. I'm here.
I've never seen an animal
with these injuries still breathing.
I'd like your permission
to put him down.
- It's. it's really the best thing...
- I... Y... You mean shoot him?
- Annie.
- Well...
Look. Liz.
The doctor's here right now...
and I can't make this decision
on my own.
- Annie. I understand that. but I have to know...
- Just do what you can.
- Okay?
- Annie. no matter what I do. this horse will never be the same.
Well. look. I. I. I. I just don't know.
It's Grace's horse. so when she...
- It's not right to make it suffer.
- I cannot deal with this now. Liz.
If you need a yes or a no.
then don't do it.
Okay? Just. just. just. just do
what you can for him. okay?
Right.
Animal should be put down.
Anybody can see that.
What did he say?
Nothing.
He's just going off duty.
Well! That's important information?
Christ.
Doctors?
I'm gonna get to know all
the nurses' names.
It's. it's good to know their names.
- I'll go get some of her things.
- I'll go.
No! I'll go.
You stay. in case she wakes up.
You guys go on ahead.
I'll be up by Christmas.
Oh. I meant to tell you. I got
those tickets for the Knicks game.
Good.
- Wanna come. Annie?
- No. Why don't you go with a friend. Grace?
Yeah.
Wanna eat something else. honey?
We can order out something else.
No. I'm just not that hungry.
That's all.
Well. you should try to eat anyway.
It's the only way you're gonna...
I said I wasn't hungry.
- Wanna watch some television?
- I think she should finish first.
- Maybe.
I just... I... I can't.
- Here.
- I'm sorry.
No. Dad! I got it. Got it.
Sorry.
- You've got to stop doing that.
- What?
Helping her all the time.
Running to her every time she trips.
anticipating her.
You know. Annie.
this didn't just happen to you.
Hi. Grace.
I don't care what he told you.
The man's a liar.
He's a actor. for God's sake.
He'd do anything to get a cover.
Gracie. what happened?
It doesn't matter. I just...
I don't wanna come back.
That's all.
Well. what are you gonna do? I mean.
you have to go to school. sweetheart.
I said no!
I don't want to come back.
That's it. I wanna go home.
Grace. listen to me.
Your leg is just healing. and you have
to give the rest of you time as well.
Is that your version of a pep talk?
Well. you're not staying home all day.
feeling sorry for yourself.
You're gonna get up.
and you're gonna figure this out.
Fine.
It's still early.
What's your next class?
Gym.
Appears to be an excellent jump.
Head and hands. eyes. perfect.
Pilgrim moves with absolute confidence
at the command of Miss MacLean.
- What is it. sweetheart?
- I wanna see Pilgrim.
- Hello. - Hi. - Hi.
It's so good to see you.
How are you doing?
- She's doing just great. Aren't you. kiddo?
- I'm fine.
Watch your step.
Mind how you go.
It's muddy back there.
Back there?
Well. what do you. what do you mean? Why
isn't he in the barn with the other horses?
Well. Grace. you see...
Pilgrim just isn't the same horse
that he used to be.
As a matter of fact. maybe now's
not the best time for you to see him.
I really wanna see him.
Can you open it. please?
Hey!
Hello. beautiful boy.
- No! No! God. no. no. please
- Grace.
- No. Grace.
- No. no. no. no. Leave me alone!
Here. Grace. Grace!
Mr MacLean. I'm so sorry.
- Dad. why didn't you tell me?
- I'm so sorry.
You should've told her. Annie.
This animal is beyond help.
Annie. can I have your permission now
to put him down?
No.
And get me every publication on riding.
racing. breeding.
Everything.
Medical publications as well.
Veterinarian journals. And tell them
it's me. and I want it now.
- Hold on. hold on. Gottschalk.
- I'll call him back.
- He says he's on his way to the airport. he really needs...
- Lucy. I'll call him back.
I'll call him back.
Just get me what I want.
"A million years before man..."
"they grazed the vast
and empty plains..."
"living by voices
only they could hear."
"They first came to know man
as the hunted knows the hunter..."
"for long before he used horses
for his labours..."
"he killed them for meat."
"The alliance with man
would forever be fragile..."
"for the fear he'd struck
into their hearts..."
"was too deep to be dislodged."
"Since that Neolithic moment..."
"when a horse was first haltered..."
"there were those among men
who understood this."
"They could see
into the creature's soul..."
"and soothe the wounds
they found there."
"The secrets uttered softly
into troubled ears."
"These men were known
as the Whisperers."
It's perfectly shot.
perfectly cropped...
perfectly laid out.
and I am so bloody bored.
Start again.
Thank you.
Would you excuse me for a moment?
Yes.
- Hello?
- Yeah. this is Tom Booker. I got a message you called.
Oh. hello. Mr Booker.
It's Annie MacLean from Cover.
You know. the magazine.
Well. thank you
for returning my call.
- Is there something I can do for you. ma'am?
- Yes. yes.
I read this article about what you do
for people with horse problems.
Well. truth is. I help horses
with people problems.
Well. whichever way
you want to put it.
This article said that you were.
you were a. a horse whisperer.
Oh. they said that? A whisperer.
And I was hoping that you'd come
to New York...
and take a look at my daughter's horse
and possibly do some...
Ma'am. I'm sorry. but I'm. I'm afraid you've
misunderstood whatever it is you read.
Because that's not exactly what I do.
I mostly conduct clinics. you see. and...
Well. could you come to New York
just for the day?
- It's only a few hours by plane.
- And I'm not doin' them now.
I'm on my way to Montana where I have
a ranch to take care of.
Well. I'd pay your fare. of course.
First class.
Ma'am. first class to Montana
is a waste of good money.
Well. if you could just give me a time
when you'd be available.
Say. am I. am I being too polite here
when I say "no" in Nevada?
Does that mean "yes" where you are?
Look. I'm really sorry for your
situation. but there's nothing I can do.
You just called the wrong person is all. I'm
sure there's some fine horse doctors back east.
No. but I don't want a horse doctor.
- I want. I want you.
- So I. I hope everything goes okay with you and your horse.
- Well. but you see. it's not my horse.
- So. so. goodbye now.
Grace?
Grace. it's Mom.
Are you all right?
I've decided about Pilgrim.
I think we should put him down.
It's not fair to let him suffer.
- Well. I think that's a very...
- Maybe they should put me down. too.
- What?
- I'm not much use anymore.
You're getting a fax.
- You're up late.
- Is it?
- How was the dinner?
- Is Grace asleep?
- Yeah. I think so.
- Nothing we haven't heard before.
Just louder this time. That's all.
- So why'd you go?
- Well. one of us had to.
They're still our friends. Annie.
Listen. I had a thought. What do you think
we go someplace warm. the three of us?
Bermuda or the Bahamas or...
What?
Nothing.
No. I just don't know if Bermuda
would be such a good idea.
- Grace would have to wear summer dresses or shorts.
- Oh. yeah. of course. of course.
What is it?
I want to take Pilgrim out to see this
horse guy. Drive him out to Montana.
- No. I'm serious.
- Now. wait a minute.
- I thought you said you didn't like the way he sounded on the phone.
- Well. I didn't.
- I want to take Grace with me.
- You're kidding!
Liz'll find me a trailer.
We can stay at motels along the way.
- What. you made arrangements already?
- No. I just checked out a few things. You know.
- Wait a minute. Drive a crazed horse all the way to Montana with...
- Oh. he's not crazed. Robert.
- Don't exaggerate.
- No. I can't just pack up and leave.
- Well. I'm not asking you to. I'll do it.
- By yourself? How?
- You can't take care of Pilgrim.
- He'll be sedated.
- I do know a thing or two about horses.
- What about the magazine?
I'm in charge.
I can oversee things from Montana.
- I can take my fax. my computer.
- Oh. you're in charge.
Well. what about Grace? The doctor says
she needs stability and security.
Well. I can't say he's being
all that effective with her.
- Are you a psychiatrist? He says it takes time.
- Well. I don't care what he says!
I cannot sit here and pretend
everything's gonna be all right.
- I am not pretending. I am trusting.
- We have to do something. Robert.
- Other people know more about this than we do.
- We are losing... We are losing her!
I don't care what the doctors say.
They don't know her.
I don't care if this doesn't sound rational.
Nobody is suggesting anything better!
I... I can't explain it. Robert.
I just have this feeling.
I just know it's the right thing.
Why. Annie?
I just know it.
Does this cowboy vet
know that you're coming?
Yeah.
What if Grace doesn't wanna go?
She will if you think she should.
- And you think it's best if I don't come.
- No. that's not what I said.
Daddy?
I don't wanna go.
Straight back. Come on.
A little closer. A little more.
Watch it. Get behind him.
Hold it! Get back! Hold it.
- Watch it!
- There he goes. Eddie!
- Why don't you get inside and...
- Lady. we're doing the best we can!
- It's the only way to load this kind of horse.
- Keep trying.
- Maybe we should give him another sedative.
- We did.
Get the gate! Get the gate!
Let's get out of here!
Hold that door!
You got a gun. just in case?
Of course not.
That's probably best.
You may want to shoot yourself
halfway to Ohio.
Grace. are you hungry?
Do you want to stop for lunch?
I don't care.
I want to find a place before
it gets dark. What do you think?
- Grace?
- Doesn't matter.
Okay. Lucy. look.
This is what I'll do.
I'll get to the next motel.
see if they have a fax and then...
Oh. wait. hang on.
I gotta go. okay? Later.
Grace. do you want
to put your music on up here?
Grace.
Do you want to put your music on
up here?
And when you purchase
your Eureka World Deluxe Vac...
Here the agricultural markets
and farm news headlines continue to...
Insecticide for small grains.
Important to always read
and follow label instructions...
This here man was rejuvenated
in the grace of the Lord.
He was washed.
Grace. look at this.
Do you wanna see that?
- I don't care.
- "I don't care."
Oh. it'll be fun. You haven't seen
any of the sights yet. It's history.
When I was 13. I used to love
doing things like this.
Oh. you were never 13. Mom.
Great idea. Mom. Now what?
- How long is this gonna go on?
- What?
You know what I mean.
Do you want us to go back home?
Is that what you want?
What are you asking me for? You didn't ask
me if I wanted to come in the first place.
Now I get to decide? Sorry.
Do you know who I'm doing this for?
I'm doing this for you.
Bullshit! It's all about you. about
you deciding. about you being right!
- It's like we work for you or somethin'!
- I don't believe this!
- How come Daddy didn't come?
- What do you mean?
You know everything.
You figure it out.
- Your father had to work.
- Yeah. right!
- Would you please stop acting like you know what you're talking about?
- You are amazing. you know?
I mean. you act like I don't even live
in that house anymore.
What. you think I don't know what's going
on? You think I'm still five years old!
- When you act like this. you are.
- How long are we gonna be away?
- I don't know. I don't know.
- Yeah. well. what if this guy can't do anything?
I don't know!
I don't have all the answers.
No. you just act like you do.
- You okay. ma'am?
- Yeah. I'm. I'm fine.
That young lady's gettin'
a little worried.
Oh. sorry. Sorry.
- Good night. ma'am.
- Good night.
You buckled up?
- Are you cold?
- A little.
You may have seen the Kennel Club champion being
rewarded with a box of chocolates the other day.
Veterinarians and humane...
But I can't get you out of my mind
Everybody...
Winter weather got you down?
Wilson Travel is offering charter
packages to sunny Orlando. Florida.
Well. looks like lots of precipitation.
as we mentioned. overnight.
Great Falls. an inch and a half. Plus. it
looks like about another half an inch.
He had an epiphany. Paul had
been transformed by the grace of God...
so he was a new creation in Christ.
Is there a man who is completely...
Hop on down to the Northern Plains
John Deere. We'll be glad to see you.
Gee. this place looks like fun.
- Don't they believe in signs around here?
- What would they say?
- "Ten miles to Big Rock. twenty miles to Bigger Rock"?
- No.
- Great trip. Mom. I'm having so much fun.
- I think I should turn here.
Oh. yeah. those rocks over there.
much more interesting.
Can we take a look at Bronty's foal
when we're done here. Dad?
Sure. as long as she don't mind.
There's this kid at school says
we should have imprint-trained him.
Says if you do it soon as they're born.
makes 'em real easy to handle later on.
That's what some folks say.
There's this thing on the TV
about a guy who does it with geese.
He has this aeroplane. and these baby geese
all grow up thinking it's their mom.
And he flies it. and they just follow.
You hear about that. Uncle T?
Yeah. Heard about it.
Well. what do you think
about all that stuff?
Well. I'll tell ya. Joey. it might be all right
for geese to grow up thinkin' they're aeroplanes...
but horses. as far as I can tell.
can't fly.
We expecting company?
- You know who it is?
- Nope.
- Mr Booker? - Yeah? - Yeah?
Tom Booker?
Annie MacLean from New York.
We talked on the phone.
I had a little bit of a hard time
finding the place. There are no signs.
Oh. there are plenty of signs.
just not many of them printed.
Why do I get the impression
that you're just not driving through?
I want you to take a look at my horse.
Now. it won't take long.
And if you still feel the same way.
then I'm sure I can find...
You thinkin' about personally
driving me back east?
Oh. no. no. no. No. I brought him along.
and my daughter. too.
We're at. we're at the Lazy J Motel.
- You hauled him all the way out here?
- Well. yeah.
I had a trailer. It's not like
I made him run alongside the car.
By yourself?
Well. ma'am. I appreciate the pains
that you've obviously gone through...
Look. please don't do
the "Shucks. ma'am" thing again.
I have just driven a few thousand miles
for a few minutes of your time.
I have brought him
all the way out here.
Just take a look at him.
If you still feel the same way...
I will be on the road by morning. and
you'll never hear from me again. okay?
Deal?
We're at the Lazy J Motel.
Whenever you're free.
You don't have to call.
Jesus!
- No. this is what you call the boonies.
- Mom. the door.
No. No. not really.
No services.
and there's one doctor in town.
But I managed to find a therapist
for Grace.
I had to drive. like. two hours.
Did they get the colour corrections?
- Yeah?
- I'm Tom Booker. Is your mother around?
She's on the phone.
She'll be right out.
- Could I...
- Mom. there's a cowboy here.
This is not Gottschalk's business.
Why is he interfering with this?
I told him I'd take care of it.
No. I told him I'd take care of it.
and I will take care of it.
I just have to get myself settled here.
Well. put it in a memo.
and I'll sign it.
- This your first time in Montana?
- Oh. no! Really?
It's completely ridiculous.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah.
yeah. yeah. I can imagine.
I can imagine. They are?
Then why did you go to meet him.
alone. secretly?
- All dressed up?
- That's. that's funny.
No. really?
I can't believe that.
- Is she gonna be long?
- Probably. She's on the phone 23 hours a day.
- What does she do?
- She's an editor.
An editor? Yeah.
Just in case she hasn't told you.
which she probably hasn't...
I don't wanna be a part of this.
okay?
Thank you.
Hi. Sorry about that.
Grace. this is Mr Booker.
Did you look at Pilgrim yet?
I was gonna take that look now.
Would you like me to come with you? I have to run
over to the office and give Mr Peterson a cheque.
- Doesn't matter.
- Grace?
Do you wanna come with us.
take a look at Pilgrim?
- Probably best she stay behind anyway.
- Okay.
- Howdy. Lester.
- Howdy.
- Goin' to see that horse?
- Yeah. I thought I might.
Well. I hope you got insurance.
That dirty son of a bitch.
Well. you're the closest
anyone's ever gotten.
I have to be honest with you.
I still feel you've made
a long trip for nothin'.
But before I even think about it...
I need to know somethin' right now.
And it's a question for Grace.
You see. when I work with a horse.
it's no good just me doin' it.
- The owner's gotta be involved. too.
- Well. that'll be a little complicated.
You can make it as complicated
or as easy as you like.
But she's the one that's gonna
be ridin' him. Am I right?
Hey? Right?
Now. here's the deal.
I don't know that I can do anything.
But I'm prepared to give it a go.
if you'll help.
- Oh. you have a problem with that?
- Isn't it. like. obvious?
Not to me.
Either you want to or you don't.
- Look. I'll talk to...
- Excuse me. With all due respect. this is her decision. not yours.
Now. I don't wanna waste
anybody's time here. mostly mine.
Well. nothin' else to do around here.
That's not good enough.
I can't help you.
What do I have to do?
I said. what do I have to do?
Well. what does she want?
- Does she want you to take care of her horse?
- Somethin' like that.
- And they're stayin' in a motel?
- The Lazy J. Can I have some butter please?
- Not exactly a tourist stop.
- Well. well. what about the girl? Doesn't she go to school?
- I don't know.
- You know. I just think she's got a lot of nerve showin' up here.
Draggin' that. you know. poor animal
and that child all the way...
Honey. don't eat with your fingers. Frank.
don't you think she's got a lot of nerve?
Well. hell. I don't know. According to
Tom. she's a pretty determined woman.
She must've thought it was worth it.
Yeah. Well. I guess they'll want
feedin'. bein' out here all day long.
- I don't think they'll expect that.
- What. they gonna drive 40 miles into town every time they want a hamburger?
- Mixed salad.
- What?
Well. I believe women from New York
eat mixed salads.
- Ain't that right. Tom?
- I believe so.
Well. that's just what we need! A vegetarian
from New York on our cattle ranch.
A Great Traveller. interested.
not merely a good one...
is a kind of introspective.
As she covers the ground outwardly...
so she advances towards fresh
interpretations of herself. inwardly.
And this is the quality
which lends Frea Starks'books...
the memorable poetic density
which is their special cachet.
Moreover. it is this quality
which makes them as fresh and strike...
You're at a good place to quit.
Oh. I got him movin' out a bit.
That's about it.
It's still a long ways away
from gettin' a leg over him.
Well. we're movin' along.
What's he doing?
Is this some kind
of physical therapy?
Hello? Hello?
What? No. you're breaking up.
Hold on. Hold on.
Don't start a fight with him.
Joey. give me your rope.
Just to pull him back. We'll never get
him outta there. Let me go in after him.
Mr Booker. I'm really not comfortable
with you taking these kind of risks.
- Oh. God!
- Hey. hey! Pilgrim!
Let him go!
Let him go.
Does that hurt you?
Only when I kick somebody.
Don't you go to school?
Taking a break.
Don't you?
School term's out early for us
so we can work the ranch.
Look at him out in the pasture.
He must've been a big.
beautiful-lookin' horse.
How was he to ride?
Excuse me.
I've got chores to look after.
Are we in the way?
Should we leave?
I guess we'll go then.
From now on.
leave your phone somewhere else.
Miss MacLean. would you and
your daughter like to stay for dinner?
Joe. take off your hat at the table.
I don't want to say it again.
Dear Lord...
we are humbly thankful
for these gifts...
for the blessings on our home.
our family and our guests.
And bless those that aren't
as fortunate.
Bless all God's creatures. Amen.
- Amen.
- Like some roast beef?
- Looks great. Thanks.
Thank you.
- Want some milk?
- Yeah. Thanks.
Ol' Hank got us
a couple more men...
to move the cattle.
And what kind of cattle
do you raise. Mr Booker?
Well. we run a mixed herd.
but mostly Black Baldies.
And what're. what're those?
- Black Angus Herefords instead of straight Herefords.
- Oh. Black Angus.
- There you go.
- Of course.
And what's.
what's the difference?
- Well. they suit the weather better.
- And their utters are black instead of pink.
They don't get burnt
with the sun bouncin' off the snow.
- They make good mothers.
- Our daddy raised straight Herefords.
You know. that's interesting.
I've always wondered every time I.
you know. when I go into a restaurant...
what's the difference between a regular
steak and a Black Angus steak?
I can never taste the difference. but I could
swear that one was more tender than the other.
I didn't know there was
that much difference between the cows.
Of course. I've never been on
a cow farm before.
Seems to me that the bulls
have the best of the time.
Just laying around the fields. waiting for somebody
to come along and ask them to do their work.
You get born a bull. got a 90% chance of
getting castrated. served up as hamburger.
So on balance.
I reckon I'd choose being a cow.
Yeah.
- Hey. young man.
- You get back up to bed!
So how's the Lazy "J"
holding up for you?
Oh. it's fine.
I still can't get used to how dark
it gets around here. though.
Every time I leave the ranch. I hold
my breath until I can see the motel.
Well. by golly.
that's a lot of drive time.
You know. Tom. while you're working
on that horse of theirs...
Annie and Grace should move
into the old creek house.
Nobody's usin' it. It's silly for her
to be driving back and forth...
when she. she don't know her way around
that well.
Well. that's very kind of you.
but really we're fine where we are.
Oh. hell. look.
I know the Lazy "J."
Whole place is as good
as falling down around your ears.
Frank. they're already
all settled in.
And anyway. I'm sure
they want their privacy.
Well. it's got doors. Diane.
and private as can be.
Tom?
I don't have a problem with it.
I think it's up to Annie.
Well. it'd be great for when my dad
comes to visit.
Where is your dad. honey?
He's at home. working.
You know... I don't know...
Is it worth it. really? I mean. how long do
you think you'll carry on working with Pilgrim?
That depends on Pilgrim.
I know. Me. too.
When are you comin' to visit?
Yeah. well. there'll be plenty of room
'cause we're moving down to the ranch.
Yeah. yeah. They've got this really cute
little house down by the creek.
It's really pretty.
Okay. Okay. I love you. too.
Ho-Hold on.
Dad wants to talk to you.
Hi.
- Well. she sounds like she's doing all right. How is she?
- Yeah.
You know. I think she seems to be getting
more comfortable on the ranch...
which is. which is the only reason
I said yes to this move.
Well. that makes sense.
So. how are you doing out there
in Marlboro country?
- Is the magazine complaining at all?
- Yeah. but nothing I can't handle.
Lucy says she thinks Gottschalk's
plotting. But what else is new?
So when are you coming home?
You know. I asked him that myself
tonight. and he doesn't know.
I miss you. Annie.
Yeah. I know. We miss you. too.
- Good night.
- 'Night.
Did you ask him to come visit?
You already did.
Do you want me to help you pack?
- Hi.
- Howdy.
What's he doing?
He's tryin' go get him
to hook on.
How's it going?
Get over there!
Ha! Come on!
Hey. you over there!
Wanna make yourself useful?
- Hey. Hank.
- Yeah?
I think you got a volunteer here.
You wanna take care of her?
Where's Grace? Grace?
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Cocktail hour yet?
- What?
I said. is it cocktail hour yet?
Come here a second.
You handled that pretty well. I think it's
time you started earning your keep around here.
So when we're not working.
you're not doing your therapy...
I'd like you to help out with the horses.
you know. rubbin' them. cleanin' the stalls.
Think you can handle that?
- That's not a question. is it?
- Nope.
Okay.
Hey. cowboy.
When I was out walkin'
one morning for pleasure
Spied a cowpuncher
come a-lopin'along
His hat was throwed back
and his spurs was a-jinglin'
And as he approached
he was singin'this song
Hey. you little ones.
How are you?
He was only 18. he had a flat
on his little pickup. and...
You know you're not allowed
to go swimming in the river.
And Marie here made the best pie.
Cherry pie. Go get some.
As luck would have it. he didn't have
all the lug nuts off...
but the jack slipped and fell
right on that rock he calls a head.
Is he okay?
Well. it rearranged his scalp
about 12 inches...
But he always dreamed of having a place
where he could raise horses...
and have a whole separate life.
My grandson Joe is named for him.
And somebody told him
about a place called Stockett.
He got on his horse
and he rode over there...
and he got off. and he walked
as far as he could one way.
And then he turned around. and he
walked as far as he could to the other.
And then he decided that
that's where he was going to settle.
And that's where we raised
Frank and Tommy.
- Where do you call home?
- She's from New York. Mom.
Well. I was born in London.
but I'm from all over really.
My father was a diplomat.
and so we moved constantly.
Oh. my.
That sounds very important.
No.
No. he was. he was a wonderful man.
He died when I was 12. but we.
we lived all over the world.
We... It's. it's not the same as.
as knowing a place like this.
Well. sometimes people carry it
more on the inside...
than the outside.
If it hadn't have been
for them troublesome doggies...
I suppose I could gather up
some of these cups and plates.
- You guys done with these?
- Yeah?
You better give me that recipe.
It was really...
I know. I know.
Be glad to tell her anything.
This family has quite a history.
Yeah. it's a story. all right.
- I love how she calls him Tommy.
- Yeah. always did.
I think she always favoured him.
She loves tellin' this story about...
when he was two years old.
he ran off...
and they found him sleepin'
in the barn...
between two giant hooves
of a Percheron stallion.
He said that horse was protectin' him.
and nobody could convince him otherwise.
Why do you always wear that hat?
'Cause it fits my head.
- Wanna try it on?
- Come on!
What do you want me to do?
What? What do you call that?
Okay. one more time.
You gonna. you gonna sit on me? Here.
So you can watch this 'cause I don't
wanna do this too many times. okay?
Put your finger up. Okay?
Okay? Loop's knotted. right?
Looks like the only way to get it off
is to break the touch. right?
Now watch. You watchin'?
Watch careful.
- Again! Again!
- Again! Again! One more time.
Oh. no. no. I don't fall
for that one twice.
Now. you guys get on in
before your mother calls you.
- Here.
- So...
Thank you.
- What?
- Do you ever sit still for just a minute?
Well. you sit still too long
in New York and you get renovated.
Why is it. Mr Booker. that sometimes I get
the feeling that you're laughing at me?
I don't know. Why?
No. You're supposed to say
you're not laughing at me.
Oh. I see. You take care of both sides
of the conversation. do you?
It's a man's world. Mr Booker.
Most women have to.
You can call me Tom.
Maybe I am laughin' a little bit.
I figure since you're here. it might
be nice to relax into the place a bit.
Yeah.
Well. it's beautiful country.
And I could see having
some kind of a...
you know. vacation place. retreat.
But I don't know how you do it
full-time.
Don't you miss
the rest of the world?
What's there to miss?
Well. if you've never lived
in a city with...
with museums and theatre and...
and restaurants and music...
well. I can't explain.
Well. does Chicago count?
- You lived in Chicago?
- That's where I met my wife.
You. you were. you were married
to a woman in Chicago?
Yeah. really. A woman.
No. I'm sorry. I didn't. I didn't...
No. I'm so...
I was studying engineering...
and she was studying music.
the cello.
And I once heard her play
a Dvorak concerto...
and I thought it was the most beautiful
piece of music I'd ever heard in my life.
So. just who's laughin' at who here?
Jogger?
I don't jog. Mr Booker. I run.
Well. that's lucky for you.
Grizzlies around here
mostly go for joggers.
You sleepin' okay in that house?
Well. I don't sleep well anywhere.
but the house is fine. yeah.
Oop. I have a way with animals.
That's all right.
He's just young.
Here. hold out your hand
just a little lower. That's it.
So he can get the smell of you.
He's beautiful.
Now. how come you don't ride anymore?
Grace told me you used to ride
when she was younger.
- She did?
- Yep.
I don't know.
No time. I guess.
I thought it was supposed to be spring.
Enjoy the day.
You. too.
Come take a ride with me.
- Can you drive?
- Drive? Not old enough.
Well. it's never too soon to start.
Here. Get in.
I... I can't.
Come on. I don't have all day.
Put the key in and turn it on.
This one?
Now. the right pedal is the gas.
The other one's the brake.
I don't think I. I can
with my with my leg.
Well. there's only one way to find out.
Now. put it in "D."
Now give it some gas.
Okay. we know you can.
Now you just gotta feel how much.
Now give it... Try it again.
There you go.
Nice.
Real nice. Now there's a little road
up at the end here. Turn onto it.
Now just follow this.
Nothin' to it.
I'm gonna kinda close my eyes here
for a little while...
so keep goin'
till you run out of road.
I... I... I don't think I can.
It's not a question if you can.
You are.
Where'd you get Pilgrim from?
We bought him in Kentucky.
Me and my mom took a trip down there
to see him.
Well. that must've been special.
Yeah.
Are you afraid of anything. Tom Booker?
Oh. growin' old.
Not bein' much use.
Hey. Grace?
What went on out there with Pilgrim?
See. Grace. I got a problem.
When I work with a horse.
I like to know its history.
Now most of the times. a horse. in its own way.
can pretty much tell you the whole story...
but sometimes they get so messed up in
their head that you need more to go on.
Now. I don't know how you feel
about talkin' about it...
and if you don't feel like it.
I understand.
But if I'm gonna figure out
what's goin' on in his head...
sure would help me if I understood
exactly what happened that day.
You know. not today.
Whenever you feel like it.
I'll leave that up to you.
- The answer's no.
- You haven't even heard the question yet.
Now. the truth is.
you'd be doin' me a real favour.
I got all these young colts
that need ridin'. Rimrock here. he's...
- I mean. he's feelin' kinda left out.
- Poor thing.
He'd be grateful.
and he'd take real good care with you.
- Is this how you're gonna make me pay my phone bill?
- No. No. ma'am.
That part's extra.
Oh. brought you a hat.
- Oh. I have a hat.
- I know. I've seen it.
- I think my stirrups are too long. or...
- No. they're fine. Just relax your centre.
- Yeah.
- Just sittin' in a bucket.
Well. it's all coming back. you know.
I mean. I'll be fine.
Okay. Well. then
I'll stop talkin' then.
No. I didn't mean that. I... You know.
I've never ridden western before.
- So...
- Yeah. but he doesn't know that. Just sit the horse.
- Yeah.
- You have a nice seat. You're doin' fine.
Thank you.
- You look good. You feel okay?
- Yeah.
- You wanna pick it up a little?
Watch your reins.
Give him some room.
Let him do the work.
- Okay? You okay?
- Yep.
Let's go.
I envy your mother.
I do.
It must be great to be her age...
and to be at the point in life
when you have no more guesswork.
No more impossible decisions to make.
And anyway. it doesn't matter because all the
worries and all the wrong turns that you made...
are as valuable and as... as...
as cherished as the things
that you did right.
I... Oh. it must be such a relief.
Must be such peace in that.
Well. I don't think you have to wait to
be her age to find that kind of peace.
Yeah. but how would you know
unless it was all behind you?
Do you have it?
Sometimes. Not all the time.
but sometimes.
When?
Wakin' up on the ranch in the morning.
knowin' what I'm supposed to do that day.
Knowing I'm home.
I wake up every morning. and
I don't know a damn thing. Was I...
Was I right to bring her here.
away from what's familiar...
away from her father. her friends?
And the more I try and fix things.
the more everything falls apart.
Maybe you should let 'em fall.
- No. I can't.
- Why?
Do you think I was right to come?
I can't answer that. Annie.
Well. I'll know soon enough. If I've
made a mistake. Grace'll let me know.
She's a strong kid.
She gets that from somebody.
Thank you for all you're doing.
You and your family.
letting us stay at the house.
It wasn't gettin' much use.
What was your wife like?
She had reddish hair.
Not. not quite. Almost.
Depended on the light.
She had green eyes.
And when she played. that was it.
Something just went right through me.
I'd never heard music like that
played before.
And the way she looked
when she played it.
And then one day. she looked at me
that way. and that was it...
for both of us.
I knew she didn't want to be a rancher's
wife. but I wanted to give it a try.
I thought maybe she could give music lessons
to the kids in town. the school maybe...
and that our kids would grow up with
my brother's kids and play together.
But she wasn't happy here.
"Too much space." she said.
- So why didn't you stay in Chicago?
- Wasn't enough space.
It just wasn't meant to be.
But how did you know. for sure?
Knowing's the easy part.
Saying it out loud's the hard part.
Seems so obvious now.
doesn't it?
"We weren't right for each other.
If only we knew then."
I didn't love her
'cause it was right.
I just loved her.
For whatever it's worth. Annie.
took a lot of guts for you to come here.
Lift your leg.
Come on. Come on.
Hey. Joe.
Hi.
Would you let me ride your horse?
- Have you talked to Tom about it?
- Of course I have.
I don't know.
You sure Tom said it's all right?
You gonna give me a hand or what?
- You sure?
- Come on.
Okay.
Easy. Hold it.
Got it. Got it. I can do it.
Here.
Are you okay?
Hey!
You better not say anything!
I thought there were too many forks.
so I just...
Oh. You look really pretty.
Thanks.
Does anybody want something to drink?
Shit!
Better go give your mom a hand.
Oh. yeah.
- Everything under control here?
- No. not really.
It's been so long
since I've done this.
I've forgotten. And
I couldn't find any Parmesan cheese.
Well. you got an easy crowd out there.
as long as it's hot.
Can I do anything?
Just make yourself comfortable.
I am comfortable.
Well. in that case
you can bring in the pasta.
- You missed a button.
- Thank you.
You know. I'll have another round
of that spaghetti. if I may.
- Oh. of course.
- Thank you.
I like the sauce.
Maybe I could get the recipe.
It's from a jar.
Well. now. you know what?
I used jar sauce once. I don't
believe it was near as good as this.
- Isn't that right. Frank?
- No.
No. You know. I think you gotta know
which brand to pick.
I sure would like the name
of this one.
Annie. you've given me
a rare night off.
You're touchin'
on a sore subject here.
Diane's got these big dreams in her head
about gettin' away to...
- Gosh. what was it? Greece. Morocco?
- Morocco.
One of these places
where women wear masks and...
everybody's runnin' around
in robes and...
- Well. we could use a vacation.
- We're going to Branson for the wedding.
- It is not. You just had a turn.
- You don't know how to play the game.
- Hey!
- Yes. I do.
You do not.
You know. Frank. You know...
Branson. Missouri
is not exactly Morocco.
I got family there. Got no family
in Morocco. far as I know.
- It's my turn.
- Is not.
- You had a turn.
- Was not.
- Was so!
- Boys. settle down.
- You're just showin' off for her.
- Shut up. stupid.
- You're the only one who's stupid. lettin' her go and fall off your horse.
- Hey. boys.
- Oh. you little turd.
- I saw 'em in the pasture. her tryin' to get on Gonzo.
- Hey. boys!
- I saw 'em.
- Oh. you turd.
Joe!
- Did you go riding?
- No!
- Get up off that floor.
- Out you go.
- Get outta here.
- Right now. Out the door.
- Go on home now.
- I didn't start it.
- My gosh!
- Here. here. Joe. Joe. Hey.
- Come on. let's go. Right now. Come on.
- Let's go.
- What's the matter with you boys?
- Annie. I'm so sorry.
They're just tired. We. we should
just get 'em home to bed.
- Say good night and thank you.
- Annie. the dinner was delicious.
- Thank you so much. It was wonderful.
- Thank you. You. say thank you.
- Thank you.
- Joe. did Grace try to ride?
I expect you should talk to Grace
about that. ma'am.
If I did anything wrong.
I'm sorry.
Don't let her turn you away.
Grace?
Is everything all right?
- Did you try riding again?
- Yeah.
Does that mean I'm cured?
Nobody's trying to cure you.
Look. I just wanna say I think
it's great that you're riding again.
- And I think I know why you needed to...
- Yeah. you know everything.
Stop it. Why won't you let me talk to you?
Why are you so angry with me?
Whatever I do. it's wrong.
Whatever I say. it's wrong.
Yeah? Well. now you know
how it feels.
Look. I... I know that
I'm hard on you sometimes.
- Right.
- And I'm sorry if that makes you feel this way.
But if I push you.
it's only because I want...
Because if I'm the perfect daughter. that
makes you the perfect mother. right?
I don't deserve that!
I don't push for me.
I push for you so that you don't spend half
your life not knowing where you belong.
Yeah? Well. you've done a great job.
Yeah.
Who's ever gonna want me like this?
Don't cry.
Nobody will.
I know it sometimes doesn't seem this way.
but I do understand what. what you're feeling.
When I was your age.
and when my. when my dad died...
I'd felt like I'd lost everything
and I'd be all alone. and...
And... But I've got you.
I used to pray every night...
that you and Dad
would have another kid...
so I wouldn't have to be
so special.
I... I know.
And I know how. how hard it must be
to have lost your best friend...
and have your body be different
than from how you'd like it to be.
But one day. somebody will look at this
extraordinary woman that you're becoming and...
all they'll see
is how much they love you.
That's all I see.
- Yep?
- Hello. this is A T& T Conference Service.
- Is this Annie MacLean?
- Yes.
I have a conference call scheduled for
you with Mr Gottschalk and Mr Felton.
Mr Felton. Hold on. please.
Okay. I'm ready.
I've been waiting for you
to come back.
Are you hungry?
Judith was.
telling me about this boy.
I never even got his name.
We were gonna go around
the railroad bridge.
We were laughing about something.
I don't know what.
And her horse fell...
and Judith's foot
was caught in the stirrup.
And she was so scared.
And next I saw this truck
coming around the turn.
And it was honking.
trying to get us to move.
And I... I tried
to grab her reins and...
to get her horse
to move out of the way.
And the truck started to skid.
And there was no time
to do anything.
It ran right into Judith. and...
And she just disappeared.
And then it came
at Pilgrim and me.
And Pilgrim reared up
at the truck.
And I fell off.
But Judith... Oh. God. Judith.
- I'm so sorry. Judith.
- Grace.
Now. I'm not gonna tell ya
it's gonna stop feelin' this bad.
But I will tell you
you didn't do anything wrong.
The same thing
could've happened to me...
or to Frank or to Joey.
And it doesn't make any sense to try
to figure out why these things happen.
There was a boy from
the Blackfeet reservation.
He used to do some work around here
for a while.
Sixteen. strong kid. good kid.
He and I were
really. really good friends.
One day he went swimmin'
and dove headfirst into the lake...
and right into a rock.
And it snapped his neck.
paralysed him.
And after the accident...
I'd look in on him
from time to time.
But he wasn't there.
It was like his mind. his spirit. whatever
you want to call it. just disappeared.
The only thing left
was just anger.
Just sort of as if the...
the boy I once knew
just went somewhere else.
I know where he goes.
I know you do.
Don't you disappear.
You do whatever you have to do
to hold on.
I'll tell you one more thing.
You know when Pilgrim
reared up against that truck?
You know what I think?
I think that damned horse loved you
so much he was tryin' to protect you.
That's what I think.
- How did you get like this?
- No. no. no. Get up.
Let me show you.
- Wanna see it again?
- Yep.
- Can you do it without smiling?
No. you can't. Not possible.
I can feel the muscles right...
- Try me.
- I can feel the muscles right...
Must be nice to have a few days
off work?
Yeah. Yeah.
It's more than a few days. though.
I'm not an editor anymore.
- First time I said it out loud.
- They fired ya?
No. no. It's more like a...
Yeah. They fired me.
- You don't seem too upset about it.
- Delayed shock.
Or maybe not.
I'm sure I can talk my way back in there
or get another magazine someplace.
But maybe I don't... Well. I'm just
not sure I... I'm not sure I want to.
Well. I guess you don't have
to figure it out till you get home.
- See. when you hit like a windmill...
- Yeah.
It's not gonna do any good.
But if you hit down.
like you can hit a golf club...
come back down. down into it.
Did you always know
this is the life you wanted?
Well. I was a rancher's daughter.
I guess it's not too far to go
to becomin' a rancher's wife. Yeah.
Yeah. Frank's a good man.
Oh. they don't come better.
I don't deny there are times I think
about all the things I won't have.
Maybe I'll get to see Morocco.
Probably not.
Did Tom have many girlfriends
after his divorce?
Hey. look. Annie.
I'm not good at this sort of talk.
Goes around and round somethin'. and never
gets to it. so let's just say what it is.
Tom means so much to this family.
Don't you go lookin' here
for whatever it is you're lookin' for.
Don't make that man go through
somethin' that took him so long...
to see his way clear of
in the first place.
I don't think Tom would do anything
he didn't want to do.
Yeah. He's a good man.
He's got a gift.
Comes from heaven above. I swear.
But he's still just a man.
Bitter raindrops glisten
On the painted Injun flower
Honey child. the mornin'
Loves you true
The muddy road
is brown and still
As far as you can see
Honey child. the noontime is...
Couldn't...
There's something I need to know.
Are you sure?
Gotta get back.
Dad?
Dad!
- Diane. It's a pleasure. Welcome.
- Diane.
- Hello. Frank.
- This is our oldest boy. Joe.
- Hi. Joe.
- And. and this is Mr Booker.
- Tom.
- Hi. Tom.
- It's a pleasure.
And I want to thank you
for the way you took in my girls here.
I can already see a difference in them.
Very grateful to you.
Dad? Dad. did you notice?
No cane.
I know. It's amazing.
- Could we show him Pilgrim. Tom?
- You bet.
- Let's go get your bags.
- Need a hand. Annie?
- Yep.
- See you later.
So at this point I'm.
I'm pretty sure I'm lost.
So I stopped by this general store and
ask if anyone knows the Booker ranch.
And this. this nice older gentleman
with a bandage on his head...
gave me directions.
Sweet Jesus. That's Henry Vanoker.
I'm surprised you didn't wind up
in Mexico.
Well. once when Dad was in India.
he. he got lost...
way. way up in these mountains.
And when he finally found his way back. everyone
said that he had discovered a new route.
And they redid all the maps.
Well. now how'd you end up
in India. Robert?
Oh. this is right after college.
I was in the Peace Corps.
Well. that's where he met Mom.
Hey. tell 'em about when
Mom went looking for Tubab.
- No. honey. I...
- Oh. Dad! Come on. Dad.
Well. Mom was a writer.
and. Dad knows the rest.
- Come on.
- She was a journalist for an English periodical.
- What was it called?
- Cambridge Monthly.
Right. And she decided to go to India
all by herself without knowing a soul.
She had no place to stay. but
she was. she was told to look up Tubab.
- Tubab?
- She comes to my door...
suitcase and typewriter...
and asks where Tubab is.
and I said. "Right here."
And she said. "You're Tubab?"
I said. "No. my name is Robert.
Tubab means white man.
and yes. I am."
And that was how we met.
Small bed.
Maybe I should sleep in the barn.
You're allergic to hay.
I... I apologize
for the surprise.
- But the days only opened yesterday. and I figured that...
- You don't have to apologize.
You have every right to be here.
You were right to bring her here.
Well. there've been plenty of times
I wasn't so sure.
Must be tired?
Yeah.
And then out here. not far from this.
I'll show you the bulls...
- Sorry about that.
- Oh. that's okay.
- I can't believe it's the same horse.
- We still have a ways to go.
So how much longer do you think?
Like I told your wife.
it's really up to Pilgrim.
- Dad. will you come dance? Please. Dad.
- All right.
Daylight has found me
Here again
You can ask me anything
But where I've been
You should know the reason
Why I called
I was lookin'for
A soft place to fall
Lookin'for a soft place
Nothin'more than a small taste
Of a love that ended
Long ago
Lookin'for a place to hide
A warm bed on a cold night
I didn't mean to hurt you
No. no. no
Lookin'out your window
At the dawn
Baby. when you wake up
I'll be gone
You're the one who taught me
After all
How to find a soft place
To fall
- The summer is really very brief.
- Oh. there's no time at all.
After I doctor those fellas. do you want me
to put them in the upper or lower pasture?
- Well. upper.
- Okay.
That's very short. very short.
You grew up here?
This is. this is where you're from?
I... I wasn't born here.
but I've always...
- The winter is real...
- I asked Annie. Of course she didn't know.
- What do you do?
- Well. of course that's the time we gotta feed cattle...
and hope the majority of'em
survive the summer here.
Is this how it's gonna be now?
You don't speak to me?
We don't speak to each other?
Well. I'm speaking to you now.
so say something.
- No.
- Why?
- I can't get in the middle of this.
- Well. I'm afraid you are in the middle of this.
- He's a good man. Annie.
- I never said he wasn't. I can't change the way I feel.
- You gotta figure out what you want.
- Do you know what you want?
I do know what I want. And I'm tryin'
real hard not to get lost in this.
I never expected
to feel this way again.
Annie. this is where I belong.
This is who I am.
Is this what you want?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Can you tell that to your family?
To Robert? To Grace?
If you had a chance to go home
and change things. would you?
You can't ask me that.
It's not that simple.
It is.
It's not fair.
No. it's not fair.
There's something
you gotta do tomorrow. boy.
He'll be okay. Grace.
Just hang on there a minute or two.
Tom will get him all right.
- What are you doing?
- Gonna have to do somethin' different. Grace.
It's not gonna hurt him. right?
Nothing we've done has hurt him.
Grace. this is Pilgrim's chance.
and it's yours. too.
Okay.
Let him get everything ready.
Come on. Grace.
Come along.
That's enough! Stop!
- Grace. this is where you come in.
- No.
Come on.
Okay. I want you
to get down here. Grace.
- Grace. I want you to come over here and sit next to me.
- But...
- But. why. why would he let me...
- Grace. look at him.
Look at him.
He's okay. And you never did anything
to let him down.
- No. No. I can't.
- Grace. listen to me.
Grace. you've gotta do this.
Trust me just one more time.
- Do what?
- I want you to come over here and sit next to me.
Start right here where the neck is and
the head. and I want you to stroke him.
I want you to rub him
and feel him all over.
That's it.
That's it. Go on ahead.
Grace.
Now we're going to show Pilgrim here
how to help you get on him.
Because. you see. there's a point where
neither of you is gonna need me anymore.
And we're there.
I'm not askin'.
Put your leg over the saddle here.
That a girl.
Now. we're gonna rock him up.
- Dad.
- Honey. you were wonderful.
Hey there! Gettin' ready
to go home. are ya?
Is Tom around?
No. he went to Sheridan to get
some horses. He left last night.
When's he coming back?
Oh. I don't rightly know.
Let me know when you need some help
loadin' Pilgrim. okay?
Yeah.
- What time's your flight?
- 12:15.
The Bookers want to leave
for the airport by 9:30.
Sure you want to drive Pilgrim back?
Well. I already know the way. and it's
not like I have a job to rush home to.
To tell you the truth.
I could use the time alone.
- When are you planning to start?
- Oh. I guess I'll leave when you and Grace go.
May I make a suggestion?
What?
Take your time.
What's the matter?
You look like there's something wrong.
I'll tell you something. Annie.
I stood there looking at that horse. and I swear
I felt like the same thing was happening to me.
And I have two choices.
I can either fight
the way things are...
or accept them.
See...
I always knew I loved you more.
Didn't bother me.
I guess I felt kind of lucky.
a little amazed that...
a woman like you would want to be
with a man like me.
And I guess I thought if I could
do everything right... If I could...
If I was the best husband I could be.
the best father...
even. even being a good lawyer only
mattered because of what it meant for us.
If I could do all that...
it wouldn't make any difference
if we loved each other the same or not.
I didn't ask for more.
I told myself I didn't need any more.
But...
the truth is. you don't know
how you feel about me.
You don't know if you want
a life with me anymore.
And the truth is...
I don't want you to come home
until you do know...
one way or the other.
Okay?
- Thanks. Joe.
- Yep.
Goodbye. Annie. Good luck to ya.
Thank you. And. and you. too.
- All right. everybody in. Frank. we all set?
- I believe so.
- I can't believe he's not here to say goodbye.
- Oh. he probably got held up is all.
No. sweetie. The truth is.
he's not real good at goodbyes.
You know. come to think of it.
not too good at hellos either.
Frank.
- You ready?
- Just a second.
- When will you be home?
- Oh. in a few days.
I'll miss you.
Well. if I get lost. you know where
to send the search party.
Could be just about anywhere.
I'll call you. okay?
- Bye.
He goin' back inside the trailer
or runnin' alongside it?
I just wanted to be here
when you left.
I don't want to leave you.
I don't want you to.
Just a few more days.
And then?
Why did this happen?
I don't ask those questions. Annie.
And I didn't ask to love you. but I do.
I'll always have that with me.
Tom.
Can we go for one last ride?
Yeah. I'll saddle 'em up.
Subtitles Diego Moraes(oakislandtk)
www.opensubtitles.org
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org